https://www.crmgismapping.ca/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
COASTAL RESOURCE MAPPING (CRM)
PRIVACY POLICY
What does CRM use your personal information for?  Information collected by CRM is used specifically for the purpose of responding to inquiries, to improve our website performance, and to personalize the delivery of information and recommended services to you. CRM does not sell your personal information to any organization, for any purpose.
Who may have access to your personal information?  Strict controls are maintained over access to personal information you share with us. Personal information is limited to employees and our suppliers who require this information to serve you.
Your personal information is secure.  At CRM, we believe that securing your personal information is a very important part of our job. That means that your contact information and other event information are always as secure as possible with us.
We need your consent.  By using the CRM information request form, you are consenting to the collection and use of information by CRM, for the purposes set out in this policy.
Changes to this Privacy Policy.  Any future changes to this Policy will be posted on the CRM website to inform visitors of what information is collected, how it is used, and under what circumstances it may be disclosed.
Do you have any questions or comments?  CRM welcomes your feedback regarding our website and/or this policy. Should you have any comments or suggestions, please contact us by email at info@crmltd.ca or by phone at
tel: 1-855-500-6610
